<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Kennedy Casey</title><link>https://kennedycasey.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in About on Kennedy Casey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://kennedycasey.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://kennedycasey.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kennedycasey.github.io/about/</guid><description>About Me PhD student, Princeton Baby Lab Department of Psychology, Princeton University
I am a first-year PhD student in Psychology at Princeton University. I work with Dr. Casey Lew-Williams in the Princeton Baby Lab. Previously, I worked with Dr. Marisa Casillas at the University of Chicago as the manager for the Chatter Lab. Broadly speaking, my research focuses on how young children&amp;rsquo;s rich and highly variable everyday language input shapes their early word representations.</description></item><item><title>Papers</title><link>https://kennedycasey.github.io/papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kennedycasey.github.io/papers/</guid><description>Papers Selected preprints Casillas, M., &amp;amp; Casey, K. (under review). Daylong egocentric recordings in small- and large-scale language communities: A practical introduction. Advances in Child Development and Behavior.
preprint
Journal Articles Casey, K., Potter, C. E., Lew-Williams, C., &amp;amp; Wojcik, E. H. (in press). Moving beyond “nouns in the lab”: Using naturalistic data to understand why infants’ first words include uh-oh and hi. Developmental Psychology, 59(11), 2162-2173.
preprint doi data</description></item><item><title>Presentations</title><link>https://kennedycasey.github.io/presentations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kennedycasey.github.io/presentations/</guid><description>Presentations Conference talks Jin, Y., Méndez Girón, J., Polian G., Casey, K., &amp;amp; Casillas, M. (2023). Vocal maturity predicts adult responsiveness in a Tseltal Mayan community. Talk presented at the Boston University Conference on Language Development. Boston, MA, USA.
abstract
Jin, Y., Méndez Girón, J., Polian G., Casey, K., &amp;amp; Casillas, M. (2023). Vocal maturity predicts adult responsiveness in a Tseltal Mayan community. Talk presented at Many Paths to Language. Nijmegen, Netherlands.</description></item></channel></rss>